wecu.com 2014-07-01

# FACTS

                                          WHATCOM EDUCATIONAL CREDIT UNION
                                                        PRIVACY POLICY
    Our Privacy Pledge. WECU® is a member focused, financial cooperative run by a board of directors you elect. Since 1936,
    the Credit Union has provided financial products and services to our members. You have trusted us with information about
    yourself and your family, and we recognize and respect your expectations of privacy. We have not and will not violate that
    trust by selling member information for solicitation or any other purpose. We will continue to strive to earn your trust and
    your business by honoring your privacy. This notice describes the privacy policy and practices followed by Whatcom
    Educational Credit Union. This notice explains what types of member information we collect and under what circumstances
    we may share it.
                               WHAT DOES WHATCOM EDUCATIONAL CREDIT UNION DO
FACTS                          WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                               Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
Why?                           consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                               how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice
                               carefully to understand Whatcom Educational Credit Union’s Privacy Policy.
What?                          The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the accounts or services
                               you have with us. This information can include:
                                     • Social Security number and income
                                     • account balances and payment history
                                     • credit history and credit scores
                               When you are no longer our member, we will not share your information except as permitted
                               or required by law as described in this notice.
How?                           All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday
                               business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                               members’ personal information; the reasons Whatcom Educational Credit Union chooses to
                               share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                         Does Whatcom Educational                  Can you limit this
Reasons we can share your personal information
                                                                             Credit Union share?                         sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
                                                                                      Yes                                     No
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
                                                                                      Yes                                     No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                                    Yes                                     No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                                       No                            We don’t share
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                                       No                            We don’t share
information about your creditworthiness
For affiliates to market to you                                                        No                            We don’t share
For non-affiliates to market to you                                                    No                            We don’t share
                                                                                 ©2013 Whatcom Educational Credit Union/Farleigh Wada Witt

What we do
How does Whatcom Educational Credit Union To protect your personal information from unauthorized
protect my personal information?          access and use, we use security measures that comply with
                                          federal law. These measures include computer safeguards
                                          and secured files and buildings. We also restrict access to
                                          nonpublic personal information about you to those
                                          employees and volunteers who need to know the information
                                          to provide products or services to you.
How does Whatcom Educational Credit Union We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal information?               open an account or apply for a loan
                                               apply for any credit union service
                                               you visit our website, provide us information on any online
                                               application or transaction, or information you send to us by
                                               email.
                                               use your credit or debit card or pay your bills
                                               make deposits to or withdrawals from your accounts
                                          We also collect your personal information from others, including
                                          credit bureaus or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?            Federal law only gives you the right to limit information sharing as
                                          follows:
                                               sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                               about your creditworthiness
                                               affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                               sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
                                          However, we do not have any affiliates with whom we share any
                                          information.
Definitions
Affiliates                                Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                          financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                               Whatcom Educational Credit Union has no affiliates.
Non-affiliates                            Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can
                                          be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                               Whatcom Educational Credit Union does not share with non-
                                               affiliates so they can market to you except for our joint
                                               marketing arrangements.
Joint marketing                           A formal agreement between Whatcom Educational Credit Union
                                          and a nonaffiliated financial company where we jointly market
                                          financial products or services to you.
                                               Our joint marketing partners include financial services and
                                               insurance companies.
Other important information
                                                                 ©2013 Whatcom Educational Credit Union/Farleigh Wada Witt

 Protecting Children’s Private Information. Our online financial services are not designed for or directed toward
 children. We do not knowingly solicit or collect data from children and we do not knowingly market to children online.
 We recognize that protecting children’s identities and online privacy is important and that responsibility rests with us and
 with parents.
Privacy Policy Changes. While we reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time, you can always review the
current version at www.wecu.com
                            Call 360.676.1168 or 800.525.8703 or TTY 800.833.6388,
                            through our InfoGuy service at www.wecu.com, or write to
Questions?                  us at: Whatcom Educational Credit Union, PO Box 9750,
                            Bellingham, WA 98227-9750
                                                                            ©2013 Whatcom Educational Credit Union/Farleigh Wada Witt
